(Howard:)Is this getting weird?
(Raj:)Hang on.
(Sheldon:)Oh, yes.
(Ira:)Hey.
(Leonard:)I just wanted to let you know
that I posted my findings.
(Sheldon:)I saw.
(Sheldon:)And I just posted
a retraction of my paper.
(Sheldon:)Now the whole scientific community
knows I was wrong.
(Leonard:)These things happen
all the time, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Not to me.
(Sheldon:)The only other retraction
I ever had to issue
(Sheldon:)was when I was seven
and I conceded that my brother
(Sheldon:)was the greatest ninja
in East Texas.
(Sheldon:)But that was just a ploy
to get my face out of his armpit.
There he is!
It's my favourite superhero,
the Retractorl
(Bernadette:)Come on,
don't give him a hard time.
I'm sorry, Cooper.
I retract it.
(Barry:)By the way, Hofstadter,
nice job disproving
the Chinese team.